{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Fire ant bites rarely cause anaphylaxis.",
					"Fire ants often bite a person repeatedly.",
					"Fire ant bites typically occur on the face.",
					"Most people are allergic to fire ant toxin."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding fire ants is correct?",
				"source": "See Common Allergens"
			},
			"back": "Fire ants often bite a person repeatedly."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"record the time and dose given.",
					"notify medical control of your action.",
					"reassess the patient’s vital signs.",
					"properly dispose of the syringe."
				],
				"question": "Immediately after giving an epinephrine injection, you should:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies"
			},
			"back": "properly dispose of the syringe."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"A direct negative effect on the body by an external substance",
					"An exaggerated immune system response to any substance",
					"Destruction of the immune system by an external substance",
					"A release of erythrocytes in response to a foreign substance"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following MOST accurately defines an allergic reaction?",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "An exaggerated immune system response to any substance"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"3 seconds.",
					"8 seconds.",
					"15 seconds.",
					"10 seconds."
				],
				"question": "When administering epinephrine via auto-injector, you should hold the injector in place for:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies"
			},
			"back": "3 seconds."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"urticaria.",
					"a pustule.",
					"purpura.",
					"a wheal."
				],
				"question": "A raised, swollen, well-defined area on the skin that is the result of an insect bite or sting is called:",
				"source": "See Common Allergens"
			},
			"back": "a wheal."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"histamine.",
					"antibody.",
					"leukotriene.",
					"allergen."
				],
				"question": "The foreign substance responsible for causing an allergic reaction is called a(n):",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "allergen."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"swelling.",
					"hives.",
					"burning.",
					"a wheal."
				],
				"question": "Urticaria is the medical term for:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "hives."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"lateral portion of the thigh.",
					"medial portion of the thigh.",
					"lateral portion of the arm.",
					"medial part of the buttocks."
				],
				"question": "When an auto-injector is used to give epinephrine, the primary injection site is the:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies"
			},
			"back": "lateral portion of the thigh."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"place her supine with her legs elevated.",
					"perform a rapid secondary assessment.",
					"assist her ventilations with 100% oxygen.",
					"locate the area where the fire ants bit her."
				],
				"question": "A 38-year-old woman was bitten by fire ants while at the park. Your primary assessment reveals that she is semiconscious; has labored breathing; and has a rapid, thready pulse. She has a red rash on her entire body, and her face is swollen. You should:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "assist her ventilations with 100% oxygen."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Wheezing",
					"Stridor",
					"Rales",
					"Rhonchi"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following sounds indicates swelling of the upper airway?",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "Stridor"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"enlargement of the bronchioles in the lungs.",
					"a significant amount of fluid in the alveoli.",
					"rapid swelling of the upper airway tissues.",
					"narrowing of the bronchioles in the lungs."
				],
				"question": "While auscultating breath sounds of a patient who was stung multiple times by a yellow jacket, you hear bilateral wheezing over all lung fields. This indicates:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "narrowing of the bronchioles in the lungs."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"scraped away from the skin.",
					"squeezed with tweezers and removed.",
					"irrigated with copious amounts of water.",
					"left in place and covered."
				],
				"question": "The stinger from a honeybee should be:",
				"source": "See Common Allergens"
			},
			"back": "scraped away from the skin."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"urticaria and angioedema.",
					"watery eyes and localized itching.",
					"hypertension and swollen hands.",
					"expiratory stridor and tachycardia."
				],
				"question": "Two of the MOST common signs of anaphylaxis are:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "urticaria and angioedema."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the patient is anxious and tachycardic.",
					"wheezing and hypotension are present.",
					"the reaction produces severe urticaria.",
					"a paramedic is present at the scene."
				],
				"question": "Epinephrine is indicated for patients with an allergic reaction when:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies"
			},
			"back": "wheezing and hypotension are present."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Diffuse urticaria",
					"Upper airway swelling",
					"Systemic vasodilation",
					"Severe hypotension"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following negative effects of anaphylaxis will be the MOST rapidly fatal if not treated immediately?",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "Upper airway swelling"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"1 hour",
					"1 minute",
					"30 seconds",
					"30 minutes"
				],
				"question": "The effects of epinephrine are typically observed within _________ following administration.",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies"
			},
			"back": "1 minute"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"persistent dry cough.",
					"abdominal cramps.",
					"drying of the eyes.",
					"flushing of the skin."
				],
				"question": "Common signs and symptoms of an allergic reaction include all of the following, EXCEPT:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "drying of the eyes."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"A 45-year-old male who ingested penicillin",
					"A 21-year-old female who inhaled pollen",
					"A 30-year-old male who was stung by a bee",
					"A 50-year-old male who was exposed to latex"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following patients would MOST likely have a delayed onset of an allergic reaction?",
				"source": "See Common Allergens"
			},
			"back": "A 45-year-old male who ingested penicillin"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"The environment in which the patient is found",
					"The patient’s family history",
					"The patient’s general physical appearance",
					"The time of year in which the exposure occurred"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following would MOST likely provide clues regarding the source of a patient’s allergic reaction?",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency"
			},
			"back": "The environment in which the patient is found"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"leukocytes and epinephrine.",
					"the bee venom itself.",
					"adrenaline and histamines.",
					"histamines and leukotrienes."
				],
				"question": "Chemicals that are responsible for the signs and symptoms of an allergic reaction to a bee sting include:",
				"source": "See Pathophysiology"
			},
			"back": "histamines and leukotrienes."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-21",
		"label": "Chapter 21"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}